[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are visiting
Uncle Pig and Auntie Pig
and Cousin Chloe.
I expect Uncle Pig
will fall asleep after lunch,
like he always does.
Daddy Pig, you shouldn't
say such things
about your own brother,
especially in front
of the children.
But it's true.
Uncle Pig always eats
too much lunch
and falls asleep,
snoring loudly, like this:
[SNORING]
[BOTH LAUGH]
DADDY PIG:
Uh, Peppa, George,
forget what I just said
about Uncle Pig.
Okay, Daddy.
[GIGGLES]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Peppa and her family
have arrived
at Uncle Pig
and Auntie Pig's house.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Auntie Pig and Uncle Pig.
Hello.
[SNORTS]
Hello, everyone.
Hello, big brother.
Uncle Pig
is Daddy Pig's brother.
Chloé Pig is Peppa
and George's cousin.
Hello, Chloé.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, George.
I want to show you
something.
Wait for us!
[KIDS GIGGLING]
This is my new
puppet theatre.
My Daddy
made it for me.
Wow.
Ooh.
I've made two puppets
already.
This one is called Chloé.
Hello. I am Chloé Pig.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
And this one
is my Daddy.
Uncle pig.
Hello, Peppa.
I am Uncle Pig.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Chloé, can me and George
make puppets too?
Yes.
Chloé paints
the puppet's eyes.
Can I do the mouth?
Okay.
My name is Peppa.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
George, what puppet
would you like to make?
Dinosaur!
A dinosaur?
George always says
dinosaur for everything.
Okay. A scary dinosaur puppet.
Chloé is making George
a dinosaur puppet.
[SNORTS]
It needs pointy teeth.
There.
A scary dinosaur.
[LAUGHS]
Grrr.
[ALL GIGGLE]
[BELL DINGS]
AUNTIE PIG: Lunchtime, everyone.
Coming.
[SNORTS]
After lunch,
we'll do a puppet show..
Hooray!
Auntie Pig has made
spaghetti for lunch.
[SLURPS]
This spaghetti
is delicious.
[SLURPS]
Best spaghetti ever.
You can tell you two
are brothers.
Alike in every way.
[SLURPING]
What do you mean?
We are completely
different.
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa, George and I are going
to do a puppet show.
Fantastic. Call us when
you're ready.
See you later.
A puppet show.
That sounds fun.
[SNORTS]
Have I got time
for some more spaghetti?
Could I have
some more too?
[ALL LAUGH]
The puppet show
is about to begin.
Hello, my name
is Chloé.
And I am Peppa.
Grrr.
Aah! It's a dinosaur.
A scary dinosaur.
Eek!
[ROARS]
Oh, I say.
That's very good.
Bravo.
I am Uncle Pig
[SNORTS]
Hello, Uncle Pig.
Hello, Peppa.
Ho, ho, ho.
[LAUGHS]
It looks just like you.
I think they've made my tummy
a bit big.
Ho, ho. I did enjoy
my lunch.
[ALL GIGGLE]
Uncle Pig, are you going
to fall asleep
and snore
like you always do?
What do you mean?
Daddy says you always
fall asleep
and snore loudly
like this.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH GASP]
[GIGGLING]
Ho, ho. Your daddy's right.
I do snore like this.
[SNORES]
Daddy Pig, you shouldn't
have said those things
about Uncle Pig.
I don't think Daddy Pig
or Uncle Pig can hear you.
[BOTH SNORING]
Daddy Pig and Uncle Pig
have fallen asleep.
You can tell
they're brothers.
[ALL LAUGH]
Eh? What happened?
[SNORTS]
Huh?
Has the puppet show
started yet?
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig is watching a
keep-fit program on television.
Come on, now.
That's right.
Bend it, stretch it,
bend it, stretch it.
[SIGHS]
I love watching telly.
What's this Mommy Pig?
It's a program about doing
exercises to keep fit.
[LAUGHS]
Thank goodness
I don't have to exercise.
I'm naturally fit.
You don't look
very fit, Daddy.
Your tummy
is a bit big.
I'm very fit.
I'll show you.
[SNORTS]
What shall I do first?
Touch your toes
like this.
Easy.
[STRAINING]
Daddy, stop pretending that
you can't touch your toes.
Uh, I'm not
pretending, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig really cannot
touch his toes.
Oh, dear, Daddy.
That's not very good.
Hmm, maybe I should do
a bit of exercise.
Yes, Daddy.
And I will start...
tomorrow.
MOMMY PIG:
Daddy Pig!
You have to start
exercising now!
Oh.
Don't worry, Daddy.
I will help you.
Oh, all right.
Peppa, you're in charge
of getting me fit.
What should I do first?
[SNORTS]
First you must do
some press-ups.
[SNORTS]
Easy.
One, two...
There.
Very good, Daddy.
Now I want you to do...
100.
One hundred?
Yes.
Come on, children.
Help me make lunch.
I'll help as well.
No, Daddy.
You've got 100 press-ups
to do.
Oh.
One.
[GIGGLES]
Two.
Three...
Mommy Pig, Peppa and George are
in the kitchen making lunch.
Daddy Pig is still
doing his press-ups.
Daddy is doing
very well.
DADDY PIG:
...Nine...10...
Yes, I do hope he's not
overdoing it.
I'll go and see.
DADDY PIG:
...13,
14, 15, 16,
17...
Daddy Pig!
You're cheating!
You should be doing
press-ups.
Oh. Uh, there was something
interesting on the TV.
Naughty Daddy.
Maybe Daddy will have
more success
with my old
exercise bike.
Ah-ha. This looks like fun.
[BELL DINGS]
I'll be able to cycle
and watch TV at the same time.
[CRANKING LOUDLY]
It's impossible.
This bike is too noisy.
I can't hear the TV.
You've got to get fit
somehow.
I know!
You can use
my bicycle.
Yes, and then you'll get
some fresh air as well.
Daddy Pig is going to ride
on Peppa's little bicycle.
Daddy, these are
the pedals.
These are the brakes.
And this is the bell.
[BELL DINGS]
Yes, yes. Thank you Peppa.
I know.
[SNORTS]
Bye-bye.
[BELL DINGS]
Easy as pie.
[PANTING]
Getting fit
is quite hard work.
[SIGHS]
[BELL DINGS]
[LAUGHS]
Now I can get fit
without having to pedal.
Daddy Pig is going
very fast.
Oh, maybe I'd better
slow down.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Aah!
The brakes aren't
strong enough.
Help! Aah!
[BELL DINGING]
[QUACKING]
Whoa!
Daddy Pig has been gone
for a long time.
Mommy, where can
Daddy be?
Don't worry, Peppa...
Daddy must be really
enjoying himself
to be away for so long.
[PANTING]
[QUACKING]
[BELL DINGING]
Daddy! Where have
you been?
I whizzed all the way
down the hill,
then I had to push the bike
all the way back up again.
Oh, poor Daddy Pig.
Well, at least I've done
my exercise.
Yes. For today.
What do you mean?
You have to do more exercise
tomorrow.
What?
Daddy, to get fit you have
to exercise every day.
Oh, no.
But don't worry, Daddy.
I'll make sure you do it.
Yes. I know you will.
[CHUCKLES]
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are in their bedroom
playing with their toys.
George, let's play
dollies and dinosaurs
[SNORTING]
Grrr!
[BOTH LAUGH]
What is that?
It looks like
a horrible monster.
Dinosaur. Grrr.
Aah! It's a dinosaur!
Help! Help!
[IMITATING DINOSAUR ROARING]
[SCREAMS]
Help! Help!
Daddy Pig is in the sitting
room reading his newspaper.
Mommy Pig is reading her book.
[LOUD THUDDING]
PEPPA:
Help!
What are they doing?
Aah! Help, help!
[LAUGHS]
Grrr.
Peppa? George?
What's going on?
[ROARS]
Aah!
[BOTH LAUGH]
What's all this noise?
Whoa!
Help! Aah!
[TOY SQUEAKS]
[SQUEAKS]
What on earth
is going on?
What a lot of noise.
And look at all this mess
on the floor.
Someone could trip over
and hurt themselves.
Someone did trip over
Oh, dear.
Poor Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Come on, children.
Let's do a bit
of tidying up.
But, Mommy, we're playing
dollies and dinosaurs.
You can play again
when you've tidied up.
But it's all
George's mess.
Is it really?
So this must be
one of George's lovely dresses?
[GASPS]
No.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, maybe some
of the mess is mine.
[ALL LAUGH]
Right. I'll help George tidy,
and Mommy Pig can help Peppa.
We can have a race.
Girls against boys.
Good idea.
Let's see who can
tidy up first.
Ready, steady, go.
[LAUGHS]
We're winning.
No, you're not.
[GIGGLES]
There.
[TOY SQUEAKS]
Oh.
What's this?
Teddy. I've been
looking for you.
Quick, Peppa.
Put Teddy in your toy basket.
[GIGGLES]
There.
Now these books.
[LAUGHING]
Lovely.
[SNORTS]
What do we have here?
Dinosaur.
That's right.
It's a dinosaur book.
It's George's pop-up
dinosaur book.
Oh!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
This is a tyrannosaurus rex.
Tyrannosaurus rex.
[BOTH LAUGH]
That's right.
Oh, this is
a brontosaurus.
Brontosaurus.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Yes.
And this is
a triceratops.
Triceratops.
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHS]
Well done, George.
George loves dinosaurs.
Daddy, George,
you've stopped tidying up.
You'll lose the race.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
Oh, yes, the race.
Come on, George.
Put this back on the bookshelf.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Daddy, you're very slow
at tidying up.
Mommy and I
are going to win.
No. We're going to win.
[CHUCKLES AND SNORTS]
We win.
No!
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
We all win.
Look how tidy
the room is.
ALL:
Hooray!
What a tidy room.
[LAUGHS]
Well done, everyone.
[SNORTS]
Mommy, now that we've tidied
our room,
can we play dollies
and dinosaurs again?
Yes, you can carry on
with your game now.
Yippee!
[SNORTS]
Where are my dolls?
Where's Mr. Dinosaur?
[BOTH LAUGH]
Here they are.
Grrr.
Dinosaur.
Aah!
It's a dinosaur!
Help! Help!
Oh, dear, the room
is untidy again.
Oh.
Well, at least it was tidy
for a bit.
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are at the
playground with their friends.
Candy Cat and Pedro Pony
are on the climbing frame.
[WHINNIES]
[MEOWS]
Suzy Sheep, Danny Dog
and Rebecca Rabbit
are playing
on the slide.
Whee!
[BLEATS]
Peppa is playing
on the swing.
[SNORTS]
Mommy, Mommy.
Push me, please.
Are you ready?
Yes, I want to go
really high.
Whee!
[GIGGLES]
Higher, Mommy.
Whee!
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
[SNORTING]
George wants to play
on the swing.
Now it's your turn,
George.
[LAUGHS]
Hold tight.
I want to push George.
Push George
gently, Peppa.
Yes, Mommy.
Hold tight, George.
[SNORTING]
Whee!
[CRIES]
Oh, dear. Peppa has pushed
George too high.
George dose not like
being up high.
Peppa, you know George
is a bit scared of heights.
Sorry, George.
[SOBS]
Let's play on
the climbing frame.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Hello, Suzy.
Hello, Danny.
Hello, Peppa.
[BLEATS]
Whee!
[LAUGHS]
[BARKS]
Whee!
You are doing it
all wrong.
This is the proper way
to swing across.
Stand back.
Ready, steady, go.
Whee!
Look at me.
I'm flying like a bird.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Oh. I can't get out.
Peppa is stuck in the tire.
[ALL LAUGH]
It's not funny.
Well, it does look
a bit funny.
[LAUGHS]
We'll have to pull you out.
Peppa's friends
are helping to free her.
[ALL LAUGHING AND MAKING
ANIMAL NOISES]
ALL:
Hooray!
Thank you, everyone.
George, do you want to play
on the climbing frame?
[SNORTING]
The climbing frame
is quite high.
George does not like
being up high.
[CRIES]
Sorry, George.
Let's play on the slide.
Yes. The slide.
[ALL LAUGH]
Yippee!
Peppa loves the slide.
Everyone loves the slide.
Mommy, Daddy,
look at me.
[SNORTS]
Ready, steady, go.
Whee!
[BLEATS]
[BARKS]
Whee!
[MEOWS]
[LAUGHS]
Whee!
[NEIGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
George wants to play
on the slide.
Are you sure, George?
It is a bit high.
[SNORTS]
All right.
I'll help you
up the steps.
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
Oh, dear.
It is a bit too high
for George.
[SOBS]
Don't worry.
I'll slide down with you.
Daddy you're too big
to go down the slide.
Don't be silly, Peppa.
I'm not too big.
[SNORTS]
Stand back.
Ready, steady, go.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL GASP]
Daddy Pig is stuck.
[ALL LAUGH]
It's not funny.
It looks very funny,
Daddy.
Hmm. I suppose it is
a bit funny.
[LAUGHS]
We'll have
to push you down.
[SNORTS]
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
Oof!
[LAUGHS]
Whee!
[BLEATS]
[BARKS]
[LAUGHS]
[MEOWS]
[NEIGHS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Daddy's tummy is just like
a bouncy castle.
[ALL LAUGH]
George loves bouncing
on Daddy's tummy.
[LAUGHING]
George isn't afraid
of heights anymore.
[PEPPA LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND LAUGHING]